(Raj:)And yes, that time,
I meant it to be dirty.
(Sheldon:)Really?
(Sheldon:)Leonard wants me back?
(Penny:)Oh, yes. He says they
are lost without you.
(Sheldon:)Well, we sure saw that coming.
(Penny:)That's right.
(Raj:)You know what
I'm going to do?
(Sheldon:)I am going to sit here
and just let them stew.
(Penny:)No, no, no. You know,
(Penny:)they have
suffered enough.
(Penny:)Everybody's
(Penny:)The thing is, you're going
to have to offer him
(Penny:)a face-saving
way out of this.
(Sheldon:)How?
(Penny:)Say you're sorry.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no.
(Sheldon:)Mrs. Mary Cooper
didn't raise her no liars.
(Penny:)Okay. Um...
(Penny:)How about this? You know
how you're always trying
(Penny:)to learn about sarcasm?
(Howard:)No.
No?
(Sheldon:)I was being sarcastic.
(Penny:)Oh. Good for you.
(Penny:)So all you have to do here
is say you're sorry to Leonard,
(Penny:)but say it
sarcastically.